[{"id": "5b174691bb2d29f81593b708", "question": "What were the name of the two space shuttles in the 1998 film \"Armageddon\"?", "answer": "Freedom and Independence", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5febd9b57e83c707845b217c", "question": "In 2016, Giants' wide receiver Odell Beckham, Jr. appeared on which television series?", "answer": "Beckham appeared as himself on a 2016 episode of the series \"Code Black\" entitled \"Hail Mary\".", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59071bde3745b36be73039c5", "question": "Who is Tony Chu\u2019s partner in the comic series \"Chew\"?", "answer": "John Colby", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a517", "question": "The city of New Orleans is on which river?", "answer": "Mississippi", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393d7", "question": "Which song became synonymous with \"The Bridge on the River Kwai\"?", "answer": "The Colonel Bogey March", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5e8a67ea9a45431f553a9cd3", "question": "What is the name of Charles Dickens' thirteenth novel?", "answer": "Great Expectations", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "58c89d23011619dd6d415483", "question": "What disappeared from the town of South Park, forcing Randy to relocate his family to a refugee camp in California?", "answer": "The Internet", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2ff", "question": "John Paul Jones' frigate was named \"Bonhomme Richard\", after whose pen name?", "answer": "Benjamin Franklin's", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fc2f1a7cee580c7f8fd1e51", "question": "Who said, \"You only live once, but if you do it right, once is good enough.\"?", "answer": "Mae West", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ec7254857c9fcac0ce7197f", "question": "What is the scientific term for the tiger species?", "answer": "Panthera Tigris", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a891", "question": "What city is home to The CN Tower?", "answer": "Toronto", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a57e", "question": "What is the capital of County Kerry, Ireland?", "answer": "Tralee", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "59ae927e574a5ce6b56b822e", "question": "What type of lettuce should be used in a classic Caesar Salad?", "answer": "Romaine", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c172", "question": "What does a dowser do?", "answer": "Find water", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5e3", "question": "What plant does the vanilla bean come from?", "answer": "The orchid", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a9b", "question": "What English author wrote the 1923 book \"Kangaroo\"?", "answer": "D.H. Lawrence", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392b2", "question": "Which actress, famous for her fruit hats, was the inspiration for the Chiquita banana logo?", "answer": "Carmen Miranda", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c05", "question": "Whose first hit single was titled \"Stubborn Kind of Fellow\"?", "answer": "Marvin Gaye's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8eb", "question": "What bay is actually the United States' largest tidal estuary?", "answer": "Chesapeake Bay", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c783", "question": "What two mammals spend their entire lives in the water?", "answer": "Whales and manatees", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c97b", "question": "Polaris is more commonly referred to as what?", "answer": "The North Star", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b063", "question": "What was the first nation in the Western Hemisphere with a woman as head of state?", "answer": "Argentina", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c071", "question": "What is the name of the kneeling cushions in churches?", "answer": "Hassock", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe12d95e39efa6330e0fecd", "question": "Which country pioneered the concept of \"Gross National Happiness\"?", "answer": "Bhutan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2a0", "question": "Which comedian created the character of Maude Frickert?", "answer": "Jonathan Winters", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fd2d6f82596a59cbdfbd3b0", "question": "Who invented the lint roller?", "answer": "Nicholas McKay", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133baec", "question": "What is the name for what an archer carries his arrows in?", "answer": "Quiver", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59f9b9cb364247bf200fb891", "question": "Who is credited with designing the icon look of the Morris Mini-Minor?", "answer": "Alec Issigonis", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad86", "question": "Who was the first person to make a public encyclopedia?", "answer": "Denis Diderot", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133beb9", "question": "Who founded \"Heiress Records\" in 2004?", "answer": "Paris Hilton", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fea4297ff048f679a45ab7a", "question": "Which age is known as the \"Age of Fish\"?", "answer": "Paleozoic Era", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339146", "question": "Who created the character Pinocchio?", "answer": "Carlo Collodi", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59049c77cf93664eb10486a7", "question": "At most, how many Friday the 13th can there be in the same calendar year?", "answer": "3", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388e9", "question": "What was writer and war hero T.E. Lawrence popularly known as?", "answer": "Lawrence of Arabia", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113392c8", "question": "Who authored the song \"In the Ghetto\"?", "answer": "Mac Davis", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3e7", "question": "What tree measurement do foresters usually make at 4 feet above ground level?", "answer": "Girth", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe8f49001dd7bf43be5e823", "question": "What is America's oldest brewery?", "answer": "Yuengling", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e4c", "question": "What athlete had a part in the movie \"Blazing Saddles\"?", "answer": "Alex Karras", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bff2", "question": "What is the principle ingredient of the dish Biryani?", "answer": "Rice", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a48f", "question": "On the bank of which river does the Portuguese capital of Lisbon stand?", "answer": "The Tagus", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391c4", "question": "In which movie does Al Pacino play a character named Ricky Roma?", "answer": "Glengarry Glen Ross", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388ea", "question": "Excluding vowels with macrons, how many letters are in the Hawaiian alphabet?", "answer": "Twelve", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a612", "question": "Which is the third largest Caribbean island?", "answer": "Jamaica", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c297", "question": "What is the name of the number system using only the symbols 1 and 0?", "answer": "The binary system", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fd96c3823c87fd04dd15e21", "question": "What Jelly Belly flavor was created for Ronald Reagan's inauguration?", "answer": "Blueberry", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bfa5", "question": "What animal provides a large portion of all the protein eaten in Peru?", "answer": "Guinea Pigs", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ad63", "question": "Which song was adopted as the national anthem of the Confederate States of America by its Congress in power?", "answer": "Bonnie Blue Flag", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe8a92c01dd7bf43be5e749", "question": "What animal is on Levi\u2019s logo?", "answer": "Horse", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388bf", "question": "What country is the setting for Shakespeare's Macbeth?", "answer": "Scotland", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5d6", "question": "Which popular candy bar is named after the maker's favorite horse?", "answer": "Snickers", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a884", "question": "At what national capital does the White Nile join the Blue Nile?", "answer": "Khartoum", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2a5", "question": "What nation was led by Peter the Great?", "answer": "Russia", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a09e", "question": "Susanne and Joanne Catherall sang with which band?", "answer": "The Human League", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5febac6b7e83c707845b20ed", "question": "How many kilometers are in an astronomical unit?", "answer": "149.6 million", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5ff51b16ff04d658268c930d", "question": "The goddess-enchantress Circe turned Odysseus\u2019 sailors into what animal?", "answer": "Pigs", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5febb6597e83c707845b2127", "question": "What is the term for when flocks of starlings swoop and swirl in unison?", "answer": "Murmuration", "category": "science"}, {"id": "594a62302ebb971c1417fb8d", "question": "Which French district does Claret come from?", "answer": "Bordeaux", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ffcfd749dc5ec6cd98a8324", "question": "What famous literary character offers this sage advice: \"Neither a borrower nor a lender be\"?", "answer": "Polonius (In\u00a0\"Hamlet\"\u00a0(Act I, Scene III),\u00a0he offers the sage advice to his son Laertes who is about to leave home.)", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c0cd", "question": "In what sport is the Heisman Trophy awarded?", "answer": "American college football", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c51a", "question": "What tart fruit has a sweet variety called \"Meyer\"?", "answer": "Lemon", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c697", "question": "In the human body, what is produced by the Islets of Langerhans?", "answer": "Insulin", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a21c", "question": "What was Dire Straits' 1982 album called?", "answer": "Love over Gold", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5a25eed16682715b82711cd1", "question": "Which European country strted colonizing Venezuela in 1522?", "answer": "Spain", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a6b", "question": "In the 1530s, Michelangelo began work on what fresco on the wall of the Sistine Chapel?", "answer": "The Last Judgement", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "59067a74ff9c0647b50a805a", "question": "In 2016, which vessel became the first solar-powered aircraft to circumnavigate the Earth?", "answer": "Solar Impulse 2", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5e94d0ff5ea27d7a1303aed3", "question": "Is the cucumber a fruit or a vegetable?", "answer": "Fruit", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a1ce", "question": "Where was Enrico Caruso born?", "answer": "Naples, Italy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fec8c56ec223966ae8f8848", "question": "The 1994 \"Leon\" was the motion-picture debut of which one of its stars?", "answer": "Natalie Portman", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c466", "question": "Which bodily organ produces urine?", "answer": "The kidneys", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b9b1", "question": "Including the end zones, how long is an NFL regulation football field?", "answer": "120 yards", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf44", "question": "How many bits was the Intel 4004 chip?", "answer": "4 bits", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b33d", "question": "Why, in 1969, did the French flag appear on some British postage stamps?", "answer": "To commemorate concorde's maiden flight", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a3f0", "question": "In which hemisphere is the Tropic of Cancer located?", "answer": "Northern", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339dfd", "question": "What \"Suddenly Susan\" actor ended up committing suicide?", "answer": "David Strickland", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c829", "question": "What is the liquid component of blood called?", "answer": "Plasma", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59071cb03745b36be73039cf", "question": "In what present-day country was the first space launch facility located?", "answer": "Kazakhstan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe73808eec85e375820b260", "question": "What is the second largest saltwater lake in the U.S.?", "answer": "Lake Pontchartrain", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a8b", "question": "What rock musician is known as \"The Motor City Madman\"?", "answer": "Ted Nugent", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b453", "question": "Which 19th century monarch ordered Buckingham House to be expanded into a royal palace?", "answer": "George IV", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ffa40e0c73aa70ea0b70b0b", "question": "Which U.S. state claims to be the diner capital of the world?", "answer": "New Jersey", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a8d", "question": "In the series \"Eragon\", what is the name of Eragon's dragon?", "answer": "Saphira", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5febba037e83c707845b2142", "question": "What is the object that opposing players must destroy in order to win at \"League of Legends\"?", "answer": "Nexus", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d4c", "question": "What actress shaved her head for her role in the movie \"The Naked Kiss\"?", "answer": "Constance Towers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59f9bb49364247bf200fb8a2", "question": "What is Eddie's last name in the TV show \"The Courtship of Eddie's Father\"?", "answer": "Corbett", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339209", "question": "What is the four-letter name of the groundhog in Groundhog Day?", "answer": "Phil", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b86c", "question": "In a game of Hearts, what term describes winning every heart and the queen of spades?", "answer": "Shooting the Moon", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc79", "question": "What company's famous plaid pattern is called \"novacheck\"?", "answer": "Burberry's", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4a7", "question": "Which country hosted the first Winter Olympic Games after World War II?", "answer": "Switzerland", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59523dab736d4be723796b46", "question": "What was the last Province or Territory that joined Canada?", "answer": "Nunavut", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b451", "question": "Edvard Munch's \"The Scream\" was stolen in 1994 and 2004 from museums in which European capital?", "answer": "Oslo", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5af250b5b63e5727cf5a4837", "question": "Which famous French civil engineer is rumoured to have designed Angola\u2019s Iron Palace?", "answer": "Gustave Eiffel", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fd969ce23c87fd04dd15e0d", "question": "What was Thomas Edison's nickname?", "answer": "The Wizard of Menlo Park", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f92", "question": "What actress earned an Oscar nomination for her first screen appearance in \"Alfie\"?", "answer": "Vivien Merchant", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339cc3", "question": "What was the one-syllable catchphrase of Little Orphan Annie's dog, Sandy?", "answer": "Arf", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1e7", "question": "Which US president lived in Peacefield?", "answer": "John Adams", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339104", "question": "What year marked the premier of Bizet's opera \"Carmen\"?", "answer": "1875", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c091", "question": "What are scaup?", "answer": "Ducks", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c50e", "question": "What color is a giraffe's tongue?", "answer": "Blue", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a67d", "question": "Wisconsin has a shoreline along which two Great Lakes?", "answer": "Superior and Michigan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a020", "question": "What did Wednesday Addams call her headless doll on \"The Addams Family\"?", "answer": "Marie Antoinette", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a0ac", "question": "What is the singer Meat Loafs real name?", "answer": "Michael Lee Aday", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338da2", "question": "What author created the character of Tom Brown?", "answer": "Thomas Hughes", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396e6", "question": "Who did Han Solo call an \"old smoothie\"?", "answer": "Lando Calrissian", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6014c520fbde8045e48466a7", "question": "The scientific name for narwhal translates to what?", "answer": "\"One tooth, one horn\" -- It is Latin for Monodon monoceros. Interesting, the whale also make a sound best described as purring.", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398ee", "question": "What movie won the 2012 Best Picture Golden Globe Award for a Drama?", "answer": "The Descendents", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5f164bb2f9b80650dbe7f92d", "question": "Which Marvel Cinematic Universe character was frozen in ice for 66 years?", "answer": "Captain America", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a1bf", "question": "Who was Charles Edward Anderson Berry better known as?", "answer": "Chuck Berry", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3d8", "question": "Who was also known as \"The Scourge of God\"?", "answer": "Attila the Hun", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133922d", "question": "What movie sees Emperor Marcus Aurelius choose Maximus to be his heir instead of his own son?", "answer": "Gladiator", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a454", "question": "Doha is the capital of which Middle-Eastern country?", "answer": "Qatar", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3b9", "question": "In what decade was Montreal Canadien great Guy Lafleur born?", "answer": "1950s", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ff2148831a458464a93c458", "question": "A sentence, verse, etc., that includes all the letters of the alphabet is called what?", "answer": "Pangram", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe65c701f3c0ead6880d615", "question": "What did the 1928 Kellogg-Briand Pact, signed by 62 nations, denounce?", "answer": "War", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b31e", "question": "Constance Markievicz, became the first ever what In 1918?", "answer": "British female MP", "category": "history"}, {"id": "597cd440e347d002c297e4ae", "question": "Which band was Rod Stewart a member of before going solo?", "answer": "Faces\u00a0", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9b1", "question": "Quito is the capital of which South American country?", "answer": "Ecuador", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a778", "question": "What former Soviet Republic lies just across the Gulf of Finland from Finland?", "answer": "Estonia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a6bc", "question": "What separates the twin cities of Minneapolis and Saint Paul?", "answer": "Mississippi River", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bb78", "question": "Before moving to Los Angeles in 1960, in what city were the NBA's Lakers franchise located for 13 years?", "answer": "Minneapolis", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a981", "question": "What London square is home to Nelson's Column?", "answer": "Trafalgar Square", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133911c", "question": "Who wrote the 1910 novel \"Howards End\"?", "answer": "E. M. Forster", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fefa4e36ce05a3942286eb8", "question": "In the film \"Ghostbusters,\" what is the occupation of Louis Tully?", "answer": "Accountant", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58b8ce6d94b094db915830a7", "question": "What is the Italian word for ice cream?", "answer": "Gelato", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b6d", "question": "Who won a Best Supporting Actor Oscar for the 2004 movie \"Million Dollar Baby\"?", "answer": "Morgan Freeman", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133929c", "question": "Apart from the piano, what other musical instrument does Dr. Sheldon Cooper from the TV show \"The Big Band Theory\"?", "answer": "The theramin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b163", "question": "Who was the 35th president of the United States?", "answer": "John F. Kennedy", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c40d", "question": "A bar that appears over a Roman numeral indicates what?", "answer": "To multiply it by 1000", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a36c", "question": "Where is Normandy?", "answer": "France", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe939a66bd93ce3a4e5f68f", "question": "What term describes the center of gravity of the Earth and moon?", "answer": "Barycenter", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b137", "question": "In what year did the Soviet Union launch its first Sputnik satellite?", "answer": "1957", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe6a81c20565ad31a57c7f3", "question": "What children's author also invented a surgical device?", "answer": "Roald Dahl", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fecca05ec223966ae8f8897", "question": "What is the name of the alien race who were the adoptive parents of Samus in the \"Metroid\" franchise?", "answer": "The Chozo", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe7c588877e98cb977789b1", "question": "What city did Frank Sinatra help immortalize as \"That Toddlin' Town\"?", "answer": "Chicago", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "600b88d91d8c1817608d53f8", "question": "Originally called pimento, what popular spice was first grown in Jamaica?", "answer": "Allspice -- It is a fruit from a tropical evergreen tree, that is dried and either sold as berries or ground up to make the spice.", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133959e", "question": "Who appears alongside Jim Carrey in the 1994 movie \"Dumb and Dumber\"?", "answer": "Jeff Daniels", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c8d9", "question": "What is produced when a magnet spins in a coil of wire?", "answer": "Electricity", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339ada", "question": "What sports team's jersey does Cameron wear in \"Ferris Bueller's Day Off\"?", "answer": "Detroit Red Wings", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5902a0c8cad1ec93f27df770", "question": "How much larger is UK pint compared to the US pint?", "answer": "About 20%, or 95 mL", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e77", "question": "Who played the blind character in the movie \"Places in the Heart\"?", "answer": "John Malkovich", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b417", "question": "Who was the first person to reach the North Pole in 1909?", "answer": "Robert Peary", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133998e", "question": "What was the first spin\u00ad-off series of the TV show \"The Cosby Show\"?", "answer": "A Different World", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aeb3", "question": "What did Thomas Blood try to steal in London in 1671?", "answer": "The Crown Jewels", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe7cd5f877e98cb97778a35", "question": "In which U.S. state are the Great Sand Dunes located?", "answer": "Colorado", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133cae4", "question": "What current-day country was writer, neurologist and psychiatrist Viktor Frankl born in?", "answer": "Austria", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b47d", "question": "What year saw the Battle of the Plains of Abraham?", "answer": "1759", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b796", "question": "What was the original flavor of the cream in Twinkies?", "answer": "Banana", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339806", "question": "By what name is the musician, Charles Hardin, better known as?", "answer": "Buddy Holly", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59e802d7de59ea584496fe99", "question": "In the TV show \"Sabrina the Teenage Witch\", what was the name of Sabrina's cat?", "answer": "Salem", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aec9", "question": "Who was the US vice-president during the presidency of Bill Clinton?", "answer": "Al Gore", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bfbf", "question": "Heroin is the brand name of morphine once marketed by which pharmaceutical company?", "answer": "Bayer", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c09e", "question": "How many gallons does a \"half butt\" barrel contain?", "answer": "63", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2e6", "question": "What year did actor W. C. Fields die?", "answer": "1946", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5922022fa4edfd43a087addd", "question": "What is the first day of Lent called?", "answer": "Ash Wednesday", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe9f165ff048f679a45aab1", "question": "How do crocodiles keep cool?", "answer": "They release heat through their mouths", "category": "science"}, {"id": "6003984d57a0e35c43f8389b", "question": "What is the term for an artistic process that involves shooting ink at a blank piece of paper?", "answer": "Bulletism\u00a0-- The result is a type of ink blot. The artist can then develop images based on what is seen.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5b69919ce762b54eb9be941b", "question": "If someone asks for your \"10-20\" over the CB radio, what are they asking for?", "answer": "Your location", "category": "general"}, {"id": "6014c94dfbde8045e48466ea", "question": "Why do pigs roll around in the mud?", "answer": "To cool down -- Pigs have very few sweat glands, so they must roll in mud to stay cool and prevent sunburns.", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339633", "question": "What Sergio Leone spaghetti western is a remake of Kurosawa's \"Yojimbo\"?", "answer": "A Fistful of Dollars", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "600243224be4723ccac22191", "question": "Charles Marlow is the narrator of which Joseph Conrad novella?", "answer": "\"Heart of Darkness\"", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ff2", "question": "Which instrument did Paganini play?", "answer": "Violin", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b003", "question": "In 1810, New York overtook what city as America's most populated city?", "answer": "Philadelphia", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c00d", "question": "What are the two primary ingredients that go into a Hollandaise sauce?\u00a0", "answer": "Butter\u00a0and egg yolks", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a64c", "question": "Which US state is home to Arches National Park?", "answer": "Utah", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5e8a67489a45431f553a9cd1", "question": "\"Shut Up and Play the Hits\" is the name of a concert movie from with U.S. music band?", "answer": "LCD Soundsystem", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5e38ce17f6c8a670a7957c52", "question": "What is Jean Valjean's prison number in the novel \"Les Miserables\"?", "answer": "24601", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a773", "question": "What is the name of the 760 \u00adfoot volcanic crater located near Honolulu, Hawaii?", "answer": "Diamond Head", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113394fd", "question": "What fictional character has a blue box that can travel through time and space?", "answer": "Doctor Who", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a868", "question": "Which countries share land borders with Spain?", "answer": "France, Portugal and Andorra", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f78", "question": "What was Buddy Holly's backing band?", "answer": "The Crickets", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a12c", "question": "Who sang the theme song to the Bond film \"The Spy Who Loved Me\"?", "answer": "Carly Simon", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339400", "question": "Who was the name of Ray Liotta's character in the 1990 movie \"Goodfellas\"?", "answer": "Henry Hill", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339055", "question": "Where was Enrico Caruso born?", "answer": "Naples, italy", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5937ec2008d98002fdd633b7", "question": "Which singer's autobiography is titled \"Take It Like a Man\"?", "answer": "Boy George's", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399b7", "question": "In what movie did Charlie Sheen play the character Bud Fox?", "answer": "Wall Street", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6018bcb0d96d05b23b28165a", "question": "Who was murdered along with OJ Simpson\u2019s estranged wife Nicole?", "answer": "Ronald Goldman", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe7c943877e98cb977789f2", "question": "Which European capital's harbor is called the Golden Horn?", "answer": "Istanbul's", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "601b4abb49076251badbeabb", "question": "Where is the oldest African-American theater located in the U.S.?", "answer": "Cleveland, Ohio -- Karamu House opened to the public in 1915. The name is Swahili, meaning \"a place of joyful gathering\".", "category": "history"}, {"id": "60173f8044491cbd7c5a17b2", "question": "Who was the first woman to cross the English Channel?", "answer": "Harriet Quimby flew across the English Channel in 1912.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ff5169eff04d658268c92f1", "question": "What activist organized the \"March of the Mill Children\" from Philadelphia to President Teddy Roosevelt's summer home in 1903?", "answer": "Mary Harris Jones -- She organized the march to demand an end to child labour.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fef5b466ce05a3942286e14", "question": "\"V-Bucks\" are the in-game currency for which famous videogame franchise?", "answer": "\"Fortnite\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1a6", "question": "In what country was the last original Volkswagen Beetle produced, in July 2003?", "answer": "Mexico", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be36", "question": "How many players are there in a standard water polo team?", "answer": "Seven", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a3b8", "question": "What nation did Afghanistan belong to until 1919?", "answer": "United Kingdom", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338907", "question": "What Canadian Island was the setting for \"Anne of Green Gables\"?", "answer": "Prince Edward Island", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c2a5", "question": "How many liters is 1 quart?", "answer": "0.946 L", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe522ce1bf59ab7d2e380eb", "question": "What is mistletoe for according to Polish folklore?", "answer": "Ward off evil", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5a4d95de08b8581f80b092a4", "question": "Which day of the week did January 1, 2017, fall on?", "answer": "Sunday", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf86", "question": "Vaccinophobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Vaccination", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113394de", "question": "What show was based on the novel \"Poor, Poor Ophelia\"?", "answer": "The Streets of San Francisco", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c176", "question": "What type of instrument is a Celesta?", "answer": "Keyboard", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a61d", "question": "Which US state is home to Petroglyph National Monument?", "answer": "New Mexico", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b5a", "question": "Who wrote the novel \"Tarzan of the Apes\"?", "answer": "Edgar Rice Burroughs", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d7d", "question": "What disease affects the protagonist in the film \"My Left Foot\"?", "answer": "Cerebral palsy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133cb08", "question": "Which planet is orbited by the moon Charon?", "answer": "Pluto", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c452", "question": "What are there 270 of in the average human baby but only 206 in an adult?", "answer": "Bones", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb3d", "question": "What type of legal defense is derived from the Latin word meaning \"elsewhere\"?", "answer": "Alibi", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390f0", "question": "Who painted \"The Boy in the Red Vest\"?", "answer": "Paul C\u00e9zanne", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5c77ce8924f0f7a362efd547", "question": "Who was Sherlock Holmes\u2019s assistant?", "answer": "Dr. Watson", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa87", "question": "Muscat is the capital of which country?", "answer": "Oman", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a8e", "question": "What was the name of Paul McCartney's backup group from 1971 to 1981?", "answer": "Wings", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe7348beec85e375820b237", "question": "Where was the first lighthouse built?", "answer": "Alexandria, Egypt", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5b7ff9393a3a814d89068c52", "question": "Which country's official language is Amharic?", "answer": "Ethiopia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338db6", "question": "In what ominous numbered room is Winston Smith strapped to a chair at the end of \"Nineteen Eighty-Four\"?", "answer": "Room 101", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a135", "question": "What is the name of Olive Oyl's mother?", "answer": "Nana Oyl", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c148", "question": "How many double stitches are there on a regulation baseball ball?", "answer": "108", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a186", "question": "In the cartoon \"Wacky Races\", who drove the Crimson Haybaler?", "answer": "The Red Max", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58ab1782baab681b09292183", "question": "What numbers appear on Donald Duck\u2019s car plate?", "answer": "313", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc2d", "question": "What is Barbie's full name?", "answer": "Barbara Millicent Roberts", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fea4638ff048f679a45aba0", "question": "The Planting Moon is found in which month?", "answer": "May", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bbf7", "question": "The feet of the infamous Pez dispenser were not added until what year?", "answer": "1978", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd9e", "question": "Who would typically use a Punnett square?", "answer": "A biologist", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ddf", "question": "From what language did English borrow the word \"alcohol\"?", "answer": "Arabic", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fea3acbff048f679a45ab2e", "question": "Atoms of the same chemical element but with different atomic masses are known as what?", "answer": "Isotopes", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5febd6a37e83c707845b216b", "question": "Which actor committed himself to solitary confinement in order to prepare for his role in the movie \"The Shawshank Redemption\"?", "answer": "Tim Robbins", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133adbe", "question": "Which war was fought along the 38th parallel?", "answer": "The Korean War", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb0d", "question": "How much does it cost to buy a railroad in the standard game of Monopoly?", "answer": "$200", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac69", "question": "What year did the Panama Canal first open?", "answer": "1914", "category": "history"}, {"id": "6014c847fbde8045e48466d5", "question": "What kind of unique fur does a platypus have?", "answer": "As if it weren't an odd enough creature, the platypus' fur is bioluminescent, meaning they can glow in the dark.", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59067e8fff9c0647b50a807c", "question": "Which artist received the most nominations for the 58th Annual Grammy Awards?", "answer": "Kendrick Lamar", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd76", "question": "What part of a pig is eaten as \"chitterlings\"?", "answer": "The intestines", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338ef4", "question": "Which literary work's title character is named Bigger Thomas?", "answer": "Native Son", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "6015e414fe83fe1f2a824bad", "question": "What was Monte Cassino?", "answer": "A large monastery in central Italy where the Germans defended Rome from Allied forces", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b918", "question": "From what animal do we get fleece?", "answer": "Sheep", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bcdb", "question": "How many squares on a side is a daily \"New York Times\" crossword puzzle?", "answer": "15", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fe69ae020565ad31a57c757", "question": "What was the first non-axis jet plane to see combat?", "answer": "Gloster Meteor", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339178", "question": "What picture hangs on Andy Dufresne's cell wall in the movie \"The Shawshank Redemption\"?", "answer": "A picture of Albert Einstein", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f031133948a", "question": "Which actress played the role of Amelie in the 2001 movie \"Amelie\"?", "answer": "Audrey Tautou", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339fba", "question": "What smash video features a vintage performance by the fictional band The Love Below?", "answer": "Hey Ya!", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339dd6", "question": "Who played the title character in the film \"The Omega Man\"?", "answer": "Charlton Heston", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5af25d94b63e5727cf5a4866", "question": "What year did Elton John originally release the song \"Candle in the Wind\"?", "answer": "1974", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe6a63520565ad31a57c7d4", "question": "What was the name of the first operational nuclear-powered submarine?", "answer": "USS Nautilus SSN-571", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133acc4", "question": "Who was the first American in space?", "answer": "Alan Shepard", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fdab48c0b8cce1e6fda7048", "question": "What is the main ingredient in falafel?", "answer": "Chickpeas", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e3b", "question": "On what TV show is Momcorp the world's largest megacorporation?", "answer": "Futurama", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a2e", "question": "What university did David Letterman graduate from in 1969 with a degree in telecommunications?", "answer": "Ball State", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fef61ab6ce05a3942286e55", "question": "Which rapper set the Guinness World Record for most words in a single hit?", "answer": "Eminem", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a500", "question": "What is the first nation you would reach after heading due east from New York City?", "answer": "Portugal", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ac39", "question": "What country's flag was Christopher Columbus sailing under when he discovered America?", "answer": "Spain's", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b39f", "question": "Who is the inventor of the cash register?", "answer": "James Ritty", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b933", "question": "What meal-in-a-box is called the San Francisco treat?", "answer": "Rice-a-Roni", "category": "general"}, {"id": "59071d5e3745b36be73039d7", "question": "What operation brought over 1,500 German scientists, engineers and technicians following the end of World War II to the US to aid in military research?", "answer": "Operation Paperclip", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0c9", "question": "In 1989, several hundred Chinese students were killed while demonstrating in what Beijing location?", "answer": "Tiananmen Square", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ad9df61e748bb36357acde8", "question": "The City of Hot Coffee is in what US state?", "answer": "Mississippi", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be91", "question": "Who hit .202 with three homers while playing outfield for the Birmingham Barons in 1994?", "answer": "Michael Jordan", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a79e", "question": "What country comprises most of the Jutland peninsula?", "answer": "Denmark", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339791", "question": "What KISS star sported the longest tongue in rock?", "answer": "Gene Simmons", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe7ca0e877e98cb97778a01", "question": "In which district of the United Kingdom is Scaffel Pike, England's highest peak, found?", "answer": "The Lake District", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113394bd", "question": "What was the name of the nightclub that Peter Gunn frequented?", "answer": "Mothers", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe7c131877e98cb97778975", "question": "Where is Grant\u2019s Tomb?", "answer": "New York City", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a042", "question": "What 2011 comedy, starring Natalie Portman, was released in France as \"Sex Friends\"\u00c9", "answer": "No Strings Attached", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5febaee37e83c707845b20f8", "question": "What year was the first black hole discovered?", "answer": "1971", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5a162b58f01ec323f8491728", "question": "Billy Joel gave a lengthy list of 20th Century events in which song?", "answer": "We Didn't Start the Fire", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1be", "question": "What US president was a personal friend of Nathaniel Hawthorne?", "answer": "Franklin Pierce", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5ab99c1f21a8909e5c332d33", "question": "Who is novelist Helen Fielding's most famous character?", "answer": "Bridget Jones", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338926", "question": "Who is the father of the Hulkling?", "answer": "Captain Marvel", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a5c4", "question": "Sleeping Bear Dunes National Park is located along the shores of what lake?", "answer": "Lake Michigan", "category": "geography"}]